stay.com 2015-12-12

# Privacy Policy - Stay.com Social City Guides

This Privacy policy shall apply in addition to and supplement Stay.com’s Terms of Service Agreement, the terms defined in the Terms of Service Agreement shall have the same meaning herein unless the context says otherwise. Click here for the Terms of Service Agreement.

User privacy is very important to Stay.com. Read this policy carefully, if you cannot agree with the terms, please don’t register with the Service.

Stay.com reserves the right to modify this Privacy policy from time to time. The most recent revision shall supersede any earlier versions and will be found on www.stay.com. It is your responsibility as a User to keep updated on the most recent changes. Continued use of the Service following the posting of any changes of the policy shall constitute acceptance of such changes. Changes that require your consent will be communicated to you.

## Stay.com and the Information We Collect From You

Stay.com is responsible for the processing of your personal data in accordance with this policy and the Norwegian Data Protection Act (LOV-2000-04-14-31).

It is voluntary to register with Stay.com and you have the right to cancel your account at any time, by contacting Stay.com.

When you create an account, you will be requested to provide Stay.com with your name and email address. It is voluntary to give away your address and phone number. Furthermore Stay.com will collect (at the User’s discretion) information pertaining to demographics such as; gender, location, marital status, travel plans, and a variety of preferential data.

When visiting the Stay.com website Stay.com will also collect information, such as but not limited to the domain that you are visiting from, the browser you are using, the duration of your visit, your IP address and the time of visit. If you as a User ask questions this information will also be saved and used by Stay.com to resolve your inquiries, and for Stay.com’s own internal resolutions.

As a User you provide Stay.com with information, much of which are travel itineraries, profiles, pictures, reviews and travel tips etc.

## How and Why Does Stay.com Use Your Information?

The collected information is saved and used to administer your account, to maintain good User and costumer care and to operate, optimize and develop the Service. As with most expanded Web communities, Stay.com also uses the information to better target content that is relevant to any particular User or groups of Users. Stay.com will only process the personal data mentioned for the purposes for which it was collected.

If you have consented thereto the information may also be used to send you tailored news and updates on the Service as well as marketing offers from Stay.com or a partner of Stay.com, which Stay.com thinks might suit you. If you no longer wish that Stay.com sends you news / updates on the Service or marketing and / or tailored offers, you may at any time change your settings. It is not Stay.com’s intention to burden its Users with undesired communication.

The registered personal data will not be saved longer than what is necessary for the purpose of the processing. As a User you agree to provide Stay.com with accurate information and to keep said information updated.

By contacting Stay.com you will be able to get information about what personal data Stay.com has registered on you. You will also upon request be able to change or update that data or require that unnecessary data be removed.

The personal data that has been registered on you will only be processed by Stay.com, and will not be shared with any third parties, except as set out in section 6 below, when required by law or when necessary in a business transaction.

With regard to the information you post on the Service you can at any time change the privacy settings to control who sees your information. See article 6 of the Terms of Service Agreement.

## Protecting User Information

Stay.com has state of the art data handling, data storage and security procedures designed to protect the personal information of Users, as well as the integrity of the platform overall. The best modern encryption and other security measures are employed to safeguard against unauthorized access to the system and to the individual accounts therein.

As a User you should be aware, that once you have published information online, cached versions indexed by search engines and other sites will be created, and that information cannot be deleted either by you or by Stay.com.

## Cookies and User Solutions

To enhance the user experience and optimize the Service, Stay.com uses “cookies”, advertising metrics, and other information gathering methods.

A “cookie” is a small text file saved on your computer to enable analysing of your use of the site. It allows Stay.com’s servers to recognize your computer and as such make the job of loading pages, identifying unique Users and browsing at the Web or a specific site faster.

If you do not want “cookies” to be used, you can at any time decline such usage by making the necessary adjustments in your web reader to instruct your browser to stop accepting cookies. However, some aspects of the Stay.com site may not function properly and you may not have an optimal user experience if you do so.

## Customer Support and Data Analysis Tools

To be able to improve the user experience at Stay.com, and in order for Stay.com to learn more about which features of the Service are being used, and how the User moves through the Service, Stay.com shall have the right to provide Stay.com's suppliers of customer support and data analysis services with personal data collected by Stay.com. The third party suppliers of such services shall process personal data in accordance with a data processing agreement entered into by the third party and Stay.com. This data processing agreement will in all material respects correspond with the terms of this Privacy policy.

Fine-grained location data will never be collected.

The collected personal data will only be accessed by Stay.com employees or third parties in co-operation with Stay.com employees. No personal information will be sold to or shared with marketers, people registries or other third parties than Stay.com's suppliers of customer support and data analysis services as set forth above.

## Questions – Contact

We welcome any questions you might have related to this Privacy policy, Stay.com or the Service. Please feel free to contact us via email, or postal mail with any inquiries:

Stay.com/EuropaReiser AS  
Gaustadalléen 21  
N-0349 Oslo
